[
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "வாய்ப்பு",
    "answers": ["வாய்ப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "நியமனம்",
    "answers": ["நியமனம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "உணர்வு",
    "answers": ["உணர்வு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "ஆராய்ச்சி",
    "answers": ["ஆராய்ச்சி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "தலைகீழ்",
    "answers": ["தலைகீழ்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "முக்கியம்",
    "answers": ["முக்கியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "நெரிசல்",
    "answers": ["நெரிசல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "சாத்தியம்",
    "answers": ["சாத்தியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "உணவுக்கடை",
    "answers": ["உணவுக்கடை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "பாத்திரம்",
    "answers": ["பாத்திரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "கத்தி",
    "answers": ["கத்தி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "சமையல்காரர்",
    "answers": ["சமையல்காரர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "பாதுகாவலர்",
    "answers": ["பாதுகாவலர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "வாய்",
    "answers": ["வாய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "மலர்கள்",
    "answers": ["மலர்கள்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "சிறுமி",
    "answers": ["சிறுமி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "அம்மா",
    "answers": ["அம்மா"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "கடைக்காரர்",
    "answers": ["கடைக்காரர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "question": "உச்சரிப்பு",
    "answers": ["உச்சரிப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "question": "கல்வெட்டு",
    "answers": ["கல்வெட்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "question": "அங்கீகாரம்",
    "answers": ["அங்கீகாரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "question": "பதிப்பகம்",
    "answers": ["பதிப்பகம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "question": "நிலநடுக்கம்",
    "answers": ["நிலநடுக்கம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "question": "அரையிறுதி",
    "answers": ["அரையிறுதி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "question": "உலகப்போர்",
    "answers": ["உலகப்போர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "question": "விழிப்புணர்வு",
    "answers": ["விழிப்புணர்வு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
